各位   我有个好消息  猜猜看
Guys! Guys! I've got great news. Guess what.
莫妮卡怀孕了
Monica's pregnant!
真的吗
Really?
当我没说过
Let's get past the moment.
-是什么好消息  -谢谢
- What's your news?  - Thank you.
我得到广告公司的工作了
I got a job in advertising.
亲爱的  这真是太棒了
Honey, that's incredible!
天啊  一个月多少钱
Gosh, what's the pay like?
哦  你们  别这样
Oh, come on, people.
如果我不知道谁赚最多
If I don't know who makes the most
我怎么知道要最喜欢谁呢
how do I know who I like the most?
嗨  乔伊
Hi, Joey.
薪水是零  是实习的工作
It pays nothing. It's an internship.
《我们的日子》也有实习生
We have interns at Days of Our Lives.
没错  就是一样的
Right. So it'll be the same,
除了不用跟你上床
except less sex with you.
你去那里做什么工作
What do you think they'll have you do there?
这只是个培训项目
It's a training program,
但是结束之后
but they hire the people
他们会雇佣他们喜欢的人
they like.
太棒了
That's great!
但无可避免的
Yeah, I mean, there's probably gonna be
会有些让人讨厌的无聊工作
some grunt work...
一个大男人还帮别人端茶倒水
which will stink. A grown man getting people coffee
得有多丢脸
is humiliating.
丢脸  却高贵
Humiliating and noble.
万分感激
Thank you.
要不是我早有工作了
You know, if I didn't already have a job
我已经在广告业做得风生水起了
I would've been good in advertising.
罗斯  "今天你喝牛奶了吗 "
Ross, you did not come up with:
不是你想出来的
''Got Milk?''
是的  是我想的  是我
Yes, I did! I did!
早知道应该写下来的
I should've written it down.
钱德勒呢
Where's Chandler?
我想要祝他第一天上班愉快
I want to wish him good luck on his first day.
而且我也闻到培根香了
And I smelled bacon.
-他刚走  -谁走了
- He just left.  - Who did?
乔伊  你不会相信的  她打来了
Joey, you're never gonna believe it! She called!
-是吗  -你得到了
- She did?  - You got it!
-是吗   -她在说什么
- I did?  - What is she talking about?
我不知道  但听起来是好事
I don't know, but it sounds great!
你的经纪人打电话来
Your agent called.
你得到试演的机会了
You got that audition!
-跟李奥·海斯吗  -是的
- With Leonard Hayes?  - Yes!
我的天啊  的确太棒了
Oh, my God, that is great!
这是一出百老汇的戏
It's for a play on Broadway.
在正经的剧院演出
And in a real theater.
不是像上次  在熟食店下面的那种
Not that little one underneath the deli like last time.
-剧本好吗  -肯定是的
- Is it a good play?  - It must be.
因为我读完之后
I read it
一个字都看不懂
and didn't understand a single word!
李奥·海斯也会参与演出
Leonard Hayes is starring in it.
是  兼导演
Yeah, and directing.
他在《麦克白》里演得好极了
He was so good in that movie of Macbeth
你看过
You saw that?
没有  但我看了预告片
No, but I saw the previews.
《蠢蛋搞怪秀》播出之前演的预告片
They played it right before Jackass.
他的作品都非常棒
He's done some amazing work.
是啊
Oh, yeah.
我喜欢他演的手机广告
I loved him in those phone commercials.
猴子用巨大的橡胶电话
When the monkey hits him in the face
打他的脸
with the giant rubber phone....
或许猴子也在试演会上
Maybe the monkey will be at the audition.
我已经够紧张了  别再让我更紧张啊
Don't make me more nervous than I already am!
大家早上好
Good morning, everybody.
我可以给您倒咖啡吗  先生
Can I get you a cup of coffee, sir?
不用  我是实习生  跟你们是一样的
Oh, no, no. I'm an intern, just like you guys.
除了我有领带  公事包
Except for the tie, the briefcase
还有我可以租车以外
and the fact that I can rent a car.
真的  你是实习生
Seriously, you're an intern?
我正准备换个行业
I'm heading in a new career direction
得从头做起嘛
and you gotta start at the bottom.
老兄
Dude.
我知道我比你们大一些
I know I'm a little older than you guys,
但不至于像鲍勃·霍普一样
but it's not like I'm Bob Hope.
那个喜剧演员  参加劳军联合组织的
The comedian. USO.
是"美利坚合众国"  先生
It's U.S.A., sir.
这位是乔伊·崔比安尼
This is Joey Tribbiani.
乔伊  这几位都是制作人
Joey, these are the producers.
还有你可能早有耳闻的
And as you probably already know,
李奥·海斯
this is Leonard Hayes.
能够见到你真是太惊喜了
It is so amazing to meet you.
我是你的超级戏迷
l am such a big fan of your work.
我是很幸运能够演出  许多很棒的角色
I've been blessed with a lot of great roles.
那还用说嘛
Tell me about it, huh?
"夜晚及周末畅聊  不限时  "
''Unlimited nights and weekends!''
你是在取笑我吗
Are you making fun of me?
我可不是在做虚假广告
Because I am not a sellout.
我不是为钱而做的
I didn't do it for money.
我相信他们的电话好用
I believe in those phones!
我表哥  差一点就死于通信服务差
I almost lost a cousin because of bad wireless service.
不  我不是在取笑你
No, I wasn't making fun of you.
我真心认为你在广告里的演出很棒
Honestly, I think you were great in those commercials.
真的
Really?
是的
Yeah.
嗯  我把角色演绎的相当有说服力
Well, I do bring a certain credibility to the role.
这倒是真的
That's true.
何止如此  当你被火箭筒射出来的时候…
Are you kidding? When they shoot you out of that cannon--
"挂掉那个电话"
''Hang up that phone!''
-一条过  -哇
- One take.  - Wow.
那我们可以开始了吗
So shall we read?
可以  当然
Oh, yeah, sure.
第二幕开始  我会出场  找到了吗
Top of Act 2. This is my entrance. You got it?
你怎么还在这里
What the hell are you still doing here?
-你知道的  -混蛋
- I think you know.  - Bastard!
这都是你造成的  你知道吗
I am what you made me. You know what?
我现在就可以走
I could go right now.
-走  走啊  -我不能
- Go! Go!  - I can't.
我想走  长暂停
Oh, I want to, Long Pause
但是我不能走
but I can't.
打断一下  你不应该把"长暂停"说出来
So sorry. You're not supposed to say ''long pause.''
我以为那是你角色的名字
Oh! Oh, I thought that was your character's name. You know?
可能是印地安人什么的
I thought you were, like, an Indian or something,
你知道的  都这样...
you know, with the....
不是  谢谢你能过来
No. Thank you so much for coming in.
我们很感激  谢谢
We appreciate it. Thank you.
你不要我再演一次吗
You don't want me to do it again?
-我可以加上口音哦  -不用了
- I could do an accent.   - No.
加上南方的口音
You know, Southern.
"阿拉可以现在奏肘  劳哥儿"  怎样
''I could go right now, mon!'' Huh?
我的老天爷啊
My God in heaven.
乔伊  你等一下
Joey, hang on.
李奥  我们可以谈一谈吗
Leonard, can we talk to you for a moment?
怎样  你是在开玩笑吧
Yes? You've got to be kidding.
他根本不会演戏
He can't act.
我不在乎你是不是觉得他很帅
I don't care if you think he's hot.
如果你想要跟他上床  随你便
lf you want to sleep with him, do it on your own time.
但这是一场戏剧表演
This is a play.
如果你坚持这样...
If you insist on this...
我会用手机快捷的通知我经纪人
I will call my agent so fast
话质清晰到  让他以为我就在隔壁
on a cell phone connection so clear, he's gonna think I'm next door!
谢谢你  这么小声帮我说话
Hi, thank you so much for whispering for my benefit.
请告诉我  我是哪里不好
Tell me what I did wrong. I'd love to work on it
我会改进  再表演一次给你看
and try it again for you.
还有  你好吗
And also, how you doing?
再给我一次机会
Give me another chance.
我真的想要进步  拜托
I really want to get better. Please?
你傍晚如果再来
If you want to come back the end of today.
这是我的建议
here are my notes.
-准备好了吗   -好了
- Ready?  - Yeah.
你太用脑子
You're in your head.
想的太多了
You're thinking way too much.
我真的很怀疑
I really doubt that.
不是  你并没有跟你的身体联系起来
No, no. It's that you're not connected with anything in your body.
没表达出迫切感
There's no urgency.
这一幕是很纠结的
The scene is a struggle.
是一种竞赛  还有
It's a race. Also,
你的表演是水平的
what you did was horizontal.
别害怕发掘垂直的情感
Don't be afraid to explore the vertical.
而且不要体会那些文字
And don't learn the words.
让文字体会你
Let the words learn you.
我不能跟制作人睡一睡就好了吗
Couldn't I just sleep with the producer?
要不要一起去吃晚餐
Hey, do you want to go to dinner tonight?
不行  我要跟女服务生约会  叫凯蒂
l can't. l've got a date with that waitress, Katie.
虽然我们只出去过两次  但我好像...
l know we've only gone out, like, twice, but l don't know...
对她的印象很不错
l have a good feeling about her.
我听到离婚的钟声了
Oh, l hear divorce bells.
钱包交出来  不然你们的麻烦就大了
Give me your wallets, and there won't be a problem.
什么
What?
我有枪
l have a gun.
好的  不要怕  菲比  保持冷静
Okay, relax, Phoebe. Just stay calm.
我的天呐  找不到我的钱包了
Oh, my God, l can't find my wallet!
好了  女士  把你的包给我了
All right, lady, now give me your purse.
不给
No.
你说不给是什么意思
What do you mean ''no''?
我就知道你会害死我的  菲比·布菲
l knew you'd be my death, Phoebe Buffay!
罗威  是你吗
Lowell, is that you?
菲比
Phoebe?
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
不可思议  我的天
Unbelievable! Oh, my God!
抱歉  罗斯
l'm sorry. Ross,
这是我流浪街头时的老朋友  罗威
this is my old friend, Lowell, from the streets!
罗威  这位是罗斯
Lowell, Ross.
罗斯  很高兴认识你
Ross, nice to meet you.
是啊  真是高兴
Yeah, a real pleasure.
真是好久了  哇  真久
lt's been so long! Oh, so long.
不敢相信你还在干这行
l can't believe you're still doing this.
我知道  但是我戒烟了
l know. But l quit smoking.
好极了
Good for you.
看起来你过得不错
You look like you're doing well.
我猜你已经金盆洗手  不抢劫了
l guess your mugging days are behind you.
我的天  菲比  你以前抢劫
Oh, my God. Phoebe, you used to mug people?
对不起  罗斯  我们老朋友正在叙旧呢
Excuse me, Ross, old friends catching up.
试演怎么样
How'd the audition go?
他们要我再去  但是…
They want to see me again, but...
李奥·海斯不喜欢我
...Leonard Hayes did not like me.
怎么了
What happened?
他说我迫切感不够
He said l wasn't urgent enough.
我演的是水平的
Everything l did was horizontal,
应该要垂直一点
and l should be more vertical.
他说我应该不要想太多
He said that l should think less.
目前为止你做的不错
Well, so far so good.
亲爱的  我老了
Honey, l'm old!
怎么了
What's wrong?
跟其他的实习生比  我太老了
I am so much older than these other interns.
拿什么和他们争
I can't compete with them.
你是年纪比较大一点没错
So you're a little older.
往好处想  你有更多的生活经历
Look at the positive. You have all this life experience.
是的  但生活经历
Yes, but I don't think life experience
帮不了我  这个
is gonna help me with these.
它们就像着火了
Wow! It's like they're on fire!
这是什么
What are they?
样品鞋
Prototype sneakers.
要我想出销售策略  我想不出来
I need ideas on how to sell them. Which I can't do...
因为但凡有自尊的成年人
...because no self-respecting adult
都不会穿这种东西的
would ever wear these.
我给你五百块  这鞋我买了
I'll give you $500 for them.
我应该怎么办呢
What am I supposed to do?
别这样  运动鞋很容易啦
Come on, sneakers are easy.
你也总穿啊
You wear them all the time.
首先  它们现在不叫运动鞋了
They're not called sneakers anymore.
改叫"霹雳鞋"或是"滑轮鞋"
They're called ''kicks'' or ''skids.''
我还听到有人说"轮鞋"
I think I heard somebody say ''slorps.''
鞋的底部有凸出的轮子
They've got wheels that pop out from the bottom
让你可以滑来滑去
so you can roll around...
因为显然  走路太耗费体力了
because apparently walking is too much exercise.
"孩子们  孩子们
''Kids! Kids!
一路滑进儿童肥胖区吧  "
Roll your way to childhood obesity!''
你可以帮我卖这些东西吗
Would you help me try to sell these?
好的  有没有想过用大波霸呢
Okay. Have you considered using a girl with huge knockers?
那不会是他们想要的
That's not what they're looking for.
那对我很有用哦
Hey, that would work on me.
你想我为什么要买婷美呢
Why do you think I buy Mrs. Butterworth's?
你都猜不到刚才怎么了
You'll never guess what just happened.
-我和菲比被打劫了  -你们没事吧
- Phoebe and I got mugged!  - Are you okay?
没事  因为菲比认识那个劫匪
Yeah. Phoebe knew the mugger.
你怎么会认识劫匪呢
How do you know a mugger?
不好意思  除了我们六个人之外
I'm sorry, I have friends
我还有其他朋友
outside the six of us.
你知道他们是怎么认识的吗
Know how she knew him?
因为菲比以前也是劫匪
Because Phoebe used to mug people.
真的吗
Seriously?
我不觉得这是什么光彩事
Well, I'm not proud of it,
但是你们知道的
but, you know...
当我流落街头的时候
...when I was living on the street
也需要钱买食物什么的
and I needed money for food and stuff....
菲比  这真是太恐怖了
Phoebe, that is awful.
我不像你们那么有钱  好吗
I wasn't rich like you guys, okay?
我没有金汤匙也没有飞天马
I didn't eat gold and have a flying pony.
我生活得很艰苦
I had a hard life.
我妈被毒贩子给杀了
My mother was killed by a drug dealer.
你妈是自杀的
Your mother killed herself.
她自己就是毒贩子
She was a drug dealer.
幸好他和菲比认识
Anyway, it was a good thing she knew him.
否则我会让他死得很难看
I was about to do some serious damage.
好吧
Okay.
一定勾起你的痛苦回忆了  罗斯
This must have brought back some bad memories for you, Ross.
-为什么  -罗斯小时候被抢过
- Why?  - Ross was mugged as a kid.
-是吗  -是的
- You were?  - Yeah.
弱小的心灵受到了严重的打击
And it was pretty traumatic.
就在圣马克漫画店外面
It was outside St. Mark's Comics.
我正在忙着
I was minding my business,
看蜘蛛侠又惹上什么麻烦了
seeing what kind of trouble Spider-Man was into.
是神奇女侠
Wonder Woman.
反正  我正去面包店的路上
Anyway, I was heading towards this bakery...
帮某人买几十个甜蛋糕
to pick up a couple of dozen linzer tortes for someone...
然后不知道从哪里冒出来的恶棍
when out of nowhere, this thug with a pipe jumps out
拿着一根管子跳出来说...
and says:
"把钱给我  笨蛋"
''Give me your money, punk!''
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
我知道  最糟糕的是
I know. And the worst part was,
他们抢走了我的背包
they took my backpack...
里面有我自己创作  亲手绘制
...which had all the original artwork
我自己的漫画
I did for my own comic book,
《科学小子》
Science Boy.
对啊  他的超能力是什么来着
Oh, yeah! What was his super power again?
一个对知识超级渴望的超人
A super-human thirst for knowledge.
我要赶去上课了
I better get to class.
你还有其他朋友
Are there any more of your friends
需要我小心的吗  菲比
I should look out for? Phoebe.
没有  事实上  你离简街远点
No. Actually, you might want to stay away from Jane Street.
那是刺客乔的地盘
That's where Stabby Joe works.
-我想我们有麻烦了  -怎么了
- I think we have a problem here.  - What?
在我当劫匪的时候
Back in my mugging days,
圣马可漫画店是我的地盘
I worked St. Mark's Comics.
-然后呢  -管子是我用的武器
- Yeah?  - A pipe was my weapon of choice...
少年和漫画书呆子  都是我的目标
...and preteen, comic-book nerds were my meat.
所以呢
So?
曾经有个小孩
There was one kid
背包上有张贴纸  写着
who had a sticker on his backpack that said:
-地质学酷毙了   -地质学酷毙了
- Geology rocks!  - Geology rocks!
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
我知道  我抢了罗斯
I know! I mugged Ross!
-你迟到了  -我知道  我很抱歉
- You're late.  - I know. I'm sorry.
我可以先跑去上个厕所吗
But can I just run to the bathroom?
不行  李奥是不等人的
No. Leonard doesn't wait.
但是我快尿出来了
But I am bursting with Yoo-hoo!
乔伊  来吧
Joey, here we go!
我们开始   快一点
Let's go. Very quickly.
我真的想要...
I really need--
现在就开始  快点
We must go now, quickly.
-好  是的  -好了吗
- Yeah. Yes, sir.  - Ready?
你怎么还在这里
What the hell are you still doing here?
你知道的
I think you know!
你这个该死的混蛋
Oh, you sick bastard!
这都是你造成的  你知道吗
I  am what you made me! Know what?
什么
What?
我可以现在就走
I could go right now.
那就走  走啊
Then go. Go!
我不能  我想走  但是我不能走
Oh, I can't. I want to, but I can't!
停  演得好
Cut. That was good!
非常精彩  这就是我想要的
Very good. You did everything I asked.
是吗
I did?
是的  而且你把这种扭曲的特质
Yes. Plus which, you've got this, I don't know, this squirmy quality
加入到这个角色中  简直出乎意料
you bring to the character I couldn't have imagined.
我们接下来可以这样
Here's what we're gonna do:
明天过来参加最后的试演
Come back tomorrow for the final callbacks.
就照你今天这样演  但是
Do all of this, what you got going now. But you know what?
加强  再加强  你可以吗
More. More. Can you do that?
当然  我没时间说谢了
Sure. I don't have time to say thank you
真的得走了
because I really gotta go!
瞧瞧他  还那么入戏  我喜欢他
Look at that! Still in character. I like him.
我播了种  无法言喻
I plant seeds. I can't explain it. I don't know.
你在做什么
Hey. What are you doing?
在试穿跑鞋
Putting on the sneakers...
融入年轻人的世界
to get in the young mindset,
看会不会激发出什么灵感
see if it sparks anything.
-发出什么了  -你听这个
- Oh, anything yet?  - Yes, how's this?
"此鞋让你的脚
''They're so uncomfortable,
不舒服到像是被踢蛋蛋"
it's like getting kicked in the nuts for your feet.''
你们可能很纳闷我在做什么
You're probably wondering what I'm doing.
不  看起来很正常
No, that seems about right.
昨天试演的时候我尿急
Yesterday at my audition, I really had to pee.
很明显  夹着尿让我演技爆发了
Apparently, having to pee makes me a good actor.
可以参加最后试演
I got a callback,
所以能喝的我都喝了  对了
so I'm drinking everything. Oh, by the way...
我们冰箱里面的蛋奶实在太好喝了
that eggnog in our fridge was great!
乔伊  那是婴儿食品
Joey, that was formula.
我们一定要多买一些
We gotta get more of that.
这东西还不赖
These aren't half bad.
你应该要向拉夫·劳伦推荐
You should suggest these to Ralph Lauren.
第一  那很蠢
Okay, first of all, that's stupid.
第二  他们不允许我跟拉夫说话
Second, I'm not allowed to talk to Ralph.
好的  我已经觉得年轻多了
All right. I feel younger already.
我的臀部好像摔伤了
Yeah, I think I broke my hip.
嘿  你来了
Hey, you!
嘿
Hey.
嘿  课上得怎样
Hey. How was class?
从来没人问过我的课  出什么事了
No one asks me that. What's wrong?
-没事  就是很想知道而已  -哦
- Nothing. I really want to know.  - Oh.
我们针对更新世
Well, there was actually a rather lively discussion
讨论得相当热烈
about the Pleistocene--
好了  我不需要这样折磨自己
All right, nothing is worth this.
我有件事要对你坦白
I have a confession to make.
你记得小时候打劫你的女生吗
Okay, you know that girl that mugged you when you were a kid?
你说什么呢  那不是女生
What are you talking about? It wasn't a girl.
是个魁梧大汉
It was this huge dude.
你用说谎  我知道是个十四岁女生
You don't have to lie anymore. I know that it was a 14-year-old girl.
不  不是
No, it wasn't.
是  是的
Yes, it was.
你认为我打不过一个十四岁女生吗
You don't think I would have defended myself against a 14-year-old--?
"把钱给我  笨蛋"
''Give me your money, punk!''
我的天  那是你
Oh, my God, it was you!
我不敢相信  是你抢劫了我
I can't believe it. You mugged me?
是的  我非常抱歉  罗斯  对不起
Yeah. And I'm so, so sorry, Ross. I'm sorry.
但如果你再想一下  这其实挺不错的
But, you know, if you think about it, it's kind of neat.
我的意思是
I mean, well,
我常常觉得自己像是个局外人
it's just that I've always felt kind of like an outsider.
你们几个人彼此都认识特别久了
You know, the rest of you have connections that go way back...
而现在  你跟我也有老交情了
...and, you know, now you and I have a great one.
这并不是好事
It's not the best!
我知道  请原谅我
I know. Please forgive me.
我不知道该说什么
I don't know what to say.
你什么都不用说
There's nothing you can say!
那是我这辈子最耻辱的事
That was the most humiliating thing ever.
甚至比...
Even more humiliating than--
我们不要说了
Let's not do this!
然后在广告结尾
And then, at the end of the commercial,
女孩们走出浴缸
the girls get out of the hot tub...
开始一起亲热
...and start making out with each other.
有趣
That's interesting.
只有一件事
Just one thought:
你没有提到鞋子
You didn't mention the shoes.
下一个是谁  钱德勒
Who's next? Chandler.
开始的画面  一个男人穿上这双鞋
You start on the image of a guy putting on the shoes.
他大约是我这个年纪
He's about my age.
-你的年纪  -对啊
- Your age?  - Aha!
他在街上滑着  接着失去了控制
He's rolling down the street and he starts to lose control.
或许他跌倒了
Maybe he falls.
或许还受伤了
Maybe he hurts himself.
就在这时候
Just then,
一个小孩  穿着这双鞋  飞快地滑过去
a kid comes flying by wearing the shoes.
他边笑边从这个男人身上跳过去
He jumps over the old guy and laughs.
接着广告词出现…
And the line reads:
"成人不宜"
''Not suitable for adults.''
钱德勒  这个很棒
Well, Chandler, that's great.
谢谢你  先生
Thank you, sir.
或是  比我小两岁的人
Or, man who's two years younger than me.
你们瞧  这才是清晰的卖点
You see, that has a clear selling point.
抓住了我们主要客户群的心态
It appeals to our key demographic.
你是怎么想出来的
How did you come up with that?
我不知道  我不知道
I don't know! I don't know!
我就是试着用年轻的心态去思考
I was just trying to get into a young mindset,
然后灵感涌动
and stuff started to flow.
太棒了  做得好
That is great. Good work.
谢谢
Thank you.
那我们大家明天见
We'll see all of you tomorrow.
天一冷  臀部就疼
The cold weather hurts my hip.
罗斯  我知道你还在生我的气
Hey, Ross. I know you're still mad at me,
但我可以跟你谈一下吗
but can I just talk to you for a sec?
当然  说吧  哦  等等
Sure, go ahead. Oh, sorry.
当然  说吧
Sure, go ahead.
我真的想要再次跟你道歉
I just really wanted to apologize again.
而且让你看些
And also show you something
你会觉得很兴奋的东西
I think you'll find very exciting.
哦  我的天啊
Oh, my God!
"街头收集来的垃圾"
''Crap from the street!''
听着  罗斯  这箱子里
Look, Ross. In this box...
都是我抢来
...are all the things I got from mugging
觉得太特别而不想卖掉
that I thought were too special to sell...
或是  抽掉的东西
or smoke.
反正  我找了一下  找到了...
Anyway, I was looking through it, and I found...
《科学小子》
Science Boy.
哦  我的天啊
Oh, my God!
我没想到还会再见到它
I never thought I'd see this again.
全部都在了
It's all here!
你为什么这些年还留着它
What made you save it all these years?
可能是我觉得它很棒
I guess I just thought it was really good.
或许有一天会值钱
And maybe it would be worth something one day.
你真的认为《科学小子》值得收藏
You really thought Science Boy was worth saving?
是的  但是你应该知道
Yeah. But you should know
我还留了一罐凡士林
I also have a jar of Vaseline
跟一副猫头骨
and a cat skull in here.
不管  这还是很惊喜
Still, this is amazing!
我的天  谢谢你  菲比
Oh, my God. Thank you, Phoebe.
不用客气  谢谢你的《科学小子》
You're welcome. Thank you for Science Boy.
我从他身上学到很多
I learned a lot from him.
你不用客气
You're welcome.
我需要答案
I need an answer!
我无法告诉你我不知道的事
I can't tell you something I don't know.
你知道的
You know!
我不知道
I don't know!
我现在就要答案
I need an answer now!
你要答案吗  答案就是...
You want an answer? The answer is....
她从未爱过我  她只爱你
She never loved me. She only loved you.
你一直都知道  而你却没有告诉我
You knew this all along and you never told me?
居然没告诉我
You never told me?
我永远都不会原谅你
I can never forgive you.
也永远都不会原谅我自己
I can never forgive you myself.
我没有活下去的必要了  砰  结束
I have nothing to live for. Bang! And scene!
精采绝伦
Absolutely amazing.
这个角色是你的了
The part is yours.
谢谢  我现在得走了
Thanks! Now I really gotta go.
不  等等  恭喜了  你办到了
No, wait! Congratulations! You did it.
你办到了  现在可以放轻松了
You did it. You can relax now. Yeah.
哇  有线电视帐单真贵
Wow! That's a big cable bill.
你没有工作
You don't have a job,
倒很敢付钱看色情片啊
but you have no problem ordering porn.
在星期六下午
On a Saturday afternoon?
我也在家耶
I was in the house!
嘿  菲比有没有提到...
Hey. Phoebe didn't by any chance mention that--
她就是那个打劫你的彪形大汉吗  有
She was the huge guy that mugged you? Yeah.
我知道了  你有没有告诉...
I see. You didn't happen to tell--
我们认识的每个人吗  我有
Everybody we know? Yeah.
太好了  谢谢
Great. Thanks.